{
    "id": "ca06e3917c034ecf978e4fe9919c9819",
    "title": "Sentence Completion",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "......................... the thief, they handed him over to the police.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Caught",
                "Having caught"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "0ceb143d3db9432fb7a2a8ab956a5a10"
        },
        {
            "question": "........................ a noise, the thief ran away.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Hearing",
                "Heard"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "ff91e3b84b4f411bbf5fa87ff8c14c90"
        },
        {
            "question": "He is ........................ to walk fast.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "too fat",
                "so fat"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "6200bc66341e408bbb7bc90f689b6d25"
        },
        {
            "question": "She was ........................ that she could not stand up.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "too tired",
                "so tired"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "dcc04366e1de46e9889996e407bd851a"
        },
        {
            "question": "...................... she left home at 4, she hasnâ€™t arrived yet.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "If",
                "As if",
                "Although"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "1441b6a346714f04ba25df2a9c4d8133"
        },
        {
            "question": "........................ the tortoise was slow, he beat the hare in the race.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "As",
                "Though"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "26ff58df4dd74fa795c1c70ba2eb1f73"
        },
        {
            "question": "..................... you reach there before 3 pm, you will not be able to meet him. /",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "If",
                "Unless"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "1a6808d4945b4c3ba18be90f89567e9c"
        },
        {
            "question": "....................... hard you may work, you cannot please him.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "However",
                "Though",
                "Even though"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "df097c4b36154a17bbd7a77228379d05"
        },
        {
            "question": "......................... his illness, he attends office regularly.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "In spite of",
                "Even though",
                "Though"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "9dcb9fe003774eb3842ada3259f91e32"
        },
        {
            "question": "The apples ..................... I bought yesterday were good.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "that",
                "which",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "82152c37aa9541ba82102f72c1410bb8"
        }
    ]
}